(Leonard:)Okay, I'm hanging up now.
(Leonard:)You know there's
no such thing as a--
(Sheldon:)No!
Penny! Penny! Penny!
(Penny:)What's the matter?
(Sheldon:)Um...
(Sheldon:)Well, I was worried
that you might be missing Leonard.
(Sheldon:)And that might be causing
you to have bad dreams,
(Sheldon:)like the kind you'd get if you
watched Clash of the Titans
(Sheldon:)right before you went to bed.
(Penny:)Sweetie, did you have a bad dream?
(Sheldon:)-To be honest, I did.
-Aw.
Back to the Future 2 was in the
Back to the Future 3 case.
(Sheldon:)Leonard did it.
(Penny:)-Good night.
-No, wait.
(Sheldon:)Perhaps I should sleep here,
so you don't miss Leonard as much,
(Sheldon:)'cause you're being
kind of a baby about it.
(Penny:)You know what?
That would make me feel better.
(Penny:)-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
(Penny:)Good night.